Man, I sure miss Julie.
我好想念茱莉
Spanish midgets.
西班牙侏儒
Spanish midgets wrestling...
西班牙侏儒摔角…
Julie.
茱莉…
Okay, yes, I see how you got there.
茱莉！我明白是怎麼想到她的
You ever figure out what that thing's for?
你有想過電話用來做什麼嗎？
Oh, see, I'm trying this new screening thing, you know?
我在過濾電話
I figure if I'm always answering the phone, people will think I don't have a life.
我想如果我老是去接的話 大家會以為我沒有生活
My God, Rodrigo never gets pinned.
老天啊，羅裡哥真是西方不敗
Hello, I'm looking for Bob.
我要找小包
This is Jade.
我是小潔
I don't know if you're still at this number, but I was just thinking about us and how great
我不知道你的電話改了沒有 不過我不斷在想…
it was.
And, well, I know it's been three years, but I was kind of hoping we could hook up again.
…可是我希望我們能夠重修舊好
You know, I barely had the nerve to make this call, so you know what I did?
我提不起勇氣打電話…
What?
什麼派對？
I got a little drunk, and naked.
我喝得茫茫的…
Bob here.
我是小包
So no one told you life was gonna be this way.
Your job's a joke, you're broke, and love life's the only way.
It's like you're always stuck in second gear.
When it hasn't been your day, why are you still here?
I'll be there for you
When the rain starts to pour
Like I've never been before
I'll be there for you
Cause you're there for me too
So, uh, what have you been up to?
你近來都在幹什麼呢？
Oh, you know, teaching aerobics
教有氣舞蹈…
Partying way too much
…玩得太瘋狂
Oh, and in case you were wondering
如果你想知道的話…
Those are my legs on the new James Bond poster
…新007電影海報上那雙腿 是我的
Can you hold on a moment? I have another call
你請等一下，我有插撥
I love her
我愛她 我知道
I know
我不知道
I'm back
So, are we gonna get together or what?
我回來了 那我們到底要不要聚一聚啊？
Uh, absolutely
當然要了
Uh, how about tomorrow afternoon?
明天下午怎麼樣？
Do you know, uh, Central Perk in the village?
Say five-ish?
Great, I'll see you then
太棒了，到時候見
Okay
Having a phone has finally paid off
我裝上電話，終於物有所值了
Okay, even though you do do a good Bob impression
就算你裝小包裝得很像…
I'm thinking when she sees you tomorrow
…等到她明天一看到你…
She may realize that, hey, you're not Bob
…就會發現你不是小包了
Ah, you see, Tattoo
Miss Jade's fantasy is to rekindle the love she once had with Bob
You know what my fantasy is?
That you talk like a normal person
I am hoping that when Bob doesn't show up
我只希望當她知道 小包放她鴿子的時候…
She will seek comfort in the open arms of the wry stranger at the next table
…她會投向鄰桌的 陌生人的懷抱
Oh my God, you are pure evil
老天，你真是邪惡到家
Okay, pure evil
邪惡到家…
Horny and alone
…飢渴兼孤單
I've done this
這我都試過了
Yeah, yeah, everybody's here
對，大家都在
Hey, everybody, say hi to Julie in New Mexico
各位，跟新墨西哥的茱莉 打聲招呼吧
Hi, Julie
茱莉…
Okay, while Ross is on the phone
趁羅斯在講電話…
Everybody owes me 62 bucks for his birthday
…每人繳62塊慶祝他的生日
Um, is there any chance that you're rounding up for...
你可不可以將就一下…
You know, like from like 20?
Hey, come on, we got the gift, the concert and the cake
少來了 要有禮物，演唱會，還有蛋糕
Do we need a cake?
蛋糕需要嗎？
Look, guys, I know it's a little steep
各位，我知道這數目多了一點
Yeah, whoosh
But it's Ross
不過是羅斯的生日呀
Yeah, it's all right
Hey, Ryan
All right, okay, I'll see you guys later
I gotta go do a thing
Okay, sweetie, I'll call you later tonight
好了，甜心，我晚上再打給你
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
Hey, hey, hey, you're not really gonna go through with this, are you?
你不是真的要那麼做吧，老兄
You know, I think I might just
我非做不可
So, uh, what are you guys doing for dinner tonight?
你們晚上吃什麼？
Well, I guess I gotta start saving up for Ross's birthday
我想我要開始 為羅斯的生日存錢了
So I guess I'll just stay home and eat dust bunnies
我的菜單是在家裡吃西北風
Can you believe how much this is gonna cost?
這個可要花很多錢啊
Do you guys ever get the feeling that Chandler and those guys
你們有時候會不會覺得…
Just don't get that we don't make as much money as they do?
…根本不明白 我們賺的錢沒他們多
Yes, yeah
Really?
It's like they're always saying, let's go here, let's go there
他們總是說 「咱們去這兒，去那兒」
Like we can afford to go here and there
好像我們真的有那個閒錢一樣
Yes, yes, and it's, and we always have to go to, you know, someplace nice
而且我們總是得去「好地方」 你知道嗎？
You know, God, it's not like we can say anything about it
Because, like, this is a birthday thing, you know, and it's for Ross
For Ross
羅斯的…
Oh, my God
老天
Hey
Hi
What?
什麼派對？
Okay, I'm at work
我在上班…
It's an ordinary day, you know, chop, chop, chop, saute, saute, saute
…跟平常的一天一樣 切切切，煎煎煎
All of a sudden, Leon, the manager, calls me into his office
突然間呢，我們經理李昂 叫我去他的辦公室
Turns out they fired the head lunch chef, and guess who got the job?
原來他們開除了午餐大廚 你們猜誰取代他的職位了？
If it's not you, this is a horrible story
如果不是你的話 這可是個糟透的故事
Fortunately, it is me
幸好，那個人是我
And they made me head of purchasing, thank you very much
他們還升我為採購主任 感激不盡
Sweet
Anyway, I just ran into Chandler and Ross downstairs
And I think we should go out and celebrate, you know, someplace nice
我認為我們該出去慶祝一下
Someplace nice
去個好地方
I'm telling you, you can't do this
說真的，你不能夠這麼做
Oh, come on, I can never get a girl like that with conventional methods
少來了，拘泥於那種傳統方法 我永遠把不到那種尤物
That doesn't matter, she wanted to call Bob
No, hey, for all we know, Bob is who she was meant to be with
她要找的是小包 小包一定是她理想的對象
You may be destroying two people's chance for happiness
你這麼做 或許會毀了兩個人快樂的機會
We don't know Bob
我們不認識小包
Okay, we know me, we like me, please let me be happy
我們認識我，我們喜歡我 拜託，讓我快樂起來
Go over there and tell that woman the truth
你過去告訴那個女人實話
All right
好吧
Go
去啊
Hi
Listen, I have to, um, ahem, I have to confess something
我要跟你招認一件事
Yes?
什麼事？
Whoever stood you up is a jerk
放你鴿子的人是混蛋
I don't know
我不知道
I just had this weird sense, you know, but that's me, I'm weird and sensitive
我就是有這種怪怪的感應 我就這樣，怪怪的又敏感
Tissue?
面紙？
Thanks
謝謝
No, you keep the pack
不用，你整包留著吧
I'm all cried out today
我今天已經「哭」干了
I don't know
我不知道
Okay, okay
Here is to my sister, the newly appointed head lunch chef
我敬我剛剛被升為 午餐大廚的老妹一杯
Who's also in charge of purchasing
而且她還接掌了採買大權
Newly appointed head lunch chef, who's also in charge of purchasing
恭賀她升為午餐大廚 並且接掌採買大權…
Who has her own little desk when Roland's not there
羅不在的時候 她有自己的小辦公桌
Lunch chef purchasing, own little desk when Roland's not there
午餐大廚，採購，羅不在時 有自己的小辦公桌
Here's to my little sister
Oh, wait, and I got a paper
Oh, cool
That's fine, I'll just wait
沒關係，我等好了
Oh, sorry
Oh, sorry, sorry
Monica
敬摩妮卡
Are we ready to order?
各位可以點菜了嗎？
Oh, you know what, we haven't even looked yet
對不起，我們還沒看菜單
Well, when you do, just let me know
那你們看過之後再叫我
I'll be right over there on the edge of my seat
我會在那邊引頸企盼的
Wow, look at these prices
你們看看這上面的價錢
Yeah, these are pretty ch-ching
是呀，都是什麼雞的
What are these, like famous chickens?
這什麼？名牌雞嗎？
Sorry I'm late
Congratulations, Mom
抱歉，我遲到了 摩妮卡，恭喜你
Thanks
謝謝
I'm not sorry I'm late
How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
我不後悔我遲到，我跟小潔的 午後約會太不可思議了
Well, pretty incredible according to the message she left for you on my machine
根據她在我答錄機上 留給你的話的確很不可思議
Hey, Chandler, why is this woman leaving a message for you on my machine?
錢德，這個女人為什麼 會在我的答錄機留話給你呢？
Oh, see, I had to tell her that my number was your number
我必須要告訴她 我的號碼是你的號碼…
because I couldn't tell her that my number was my number
…因為我不能告訴她 我的號碼是我的號碼…
because she thinks that my number is Bob's number
…因為她以為 我的號碼是小包的號碼
Hey, tell me again, what do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
你再告訴我一次 羅先生打來的時候我怎麼辦？
Do I dare ask?
可以點菜了嗎？
Yes, I'll start with the carpaccio and then I'll have the grilled prawns
好，我要先來一份生牛肉 然後再來一份烤蝦
That sounds great, same for me
聽起來不錯，我也一樣
And for the gentleman?
那這位先生呢？
Yeah, I'll have the Thai chicken pizza
我要泰國雞肉披薩
But hey, look, if I get it without the knots and leaks and stuff, is it cheaper?
如果我的披薩少加乾果，大蒜…
You'd think, wouldn't you?
你是那麼想嗎？
Miss?
面紙？
Okay, I will have the side salad
好了，我想要點…伴碟沙拉
And what would that be on the side of?
那要伴在什麼菜旁邊呢？
I don't know, why don't you just put it right here next to my water?
你就幫我放在我的水旁邊好了
And for you?
那你呢？
Um, I'm gonna have a cup of the cucumber soup and, um, take care
我想我要來一碗黃瓜湯…
I will have the Cajun catfish
我要一份紐奧良鯰魚
Anything else?
就這樣嗎？
Yes, how about a verse of Killing Me Softly?
還有一首「情歌迷死人」 怎麼樣？
You're gonna sneeze on my fish, aren't you?
你會朝我的魚打噴嚏 對不對？
Whoa, does anybody else feel like they just gave birth to an alien?
Yes
什麼事？
No
不行
K plus tip divided by six, and everyone owes twenty-eight bucks
Um, everyone?
每個人？
Oh, you're right, I'm sorry
你說得對，對不起
Thank you
謝了
It's Monica's big night, she shouldn't pay
今天是摩妮卡的大日子 她不需要付啊
Oh, thank you
謝謝
So five of us is thirty-three fifty apiece
No, uh-uh, no way, sorry, not gonna happen
不行，抱歉 那是不可能的事
Whoa, whoa, prom night flashback
畢業舞會重演
I'm sorry, Monica, I'm really happy you got promoted, but cold cucumber mush for thirty-something bucks?
No, Rachel just had that little salad, and Joey with his, like, teeny pizza
Okay, Pheebs, how about we'll each just pay for what we had, okay? It's no big deal
那我們就各付各的，好嗎？
Not for you
對你來講就是
Alright, what's going on?
到底怎麼了？
Okay, look, you guys, I really don't want to get into this right now, I think it'll just make everybody uncomfortable
Alright, alright, you're fine, alright
Whoa, whoa, you can tell us
拜託，說出來吧
Yeah, hello, it's us, alright, we'll be fine
對啊，是我們，沒關係的
Yeah
Okay, um, uh, we three feel like that, um, sometimes you guys don't get that, uh
Ahem
We don't have as much money as you
我們沒你們那麼有錢
Okay
I hear ya
我懂了
We can talk about that
那我們可以談啊
Well, then, let's
那麼…
What?
什麼派對？
Well, um, I, I guess I just never think of money as an issue
我猜我只是 從沒想過錢是個問題
That's cause you have it
That's a good point
So, um, how come you guys haven't talked about this before?
你們以前為何提出來討論呢？
Cause it's always something, you know, like with Monica's new job, or the whole Ross's birthday hoopla
因為總是有特別的事情 像摩妮卡的新工作…
What?
什麼派對？
Whoa, hey, I don't want my birthday to be the source of any kind of negative, there's gonna be a hoopla?
我可不希望我的生日 造成任何的不愉快…
Basically, there's the thing, and then there's the stuff after the thing, and it's, if it makes anybody feel better, then we can just forget the thing, and we'll just do the gift
Gift? The thing's not the gift?
禮物？禮物不就是那件事嗎？
No, the thing was, we were gonna go see Hootie and the Blowfish
不，那件事就是我們要去看 「混混與自大狂」
Hootie and, oh my, I, I, I can catch them on the radio
我可以聽收音機就好了
No, now I feel bad, you wanna go to the concert
不，現在我愧疚了 你想去聽那場演唱會的？
No, look, hey, it's my birthday, and the important thing is that we all be together
…最重要的 是我們大家一起過
All of us
Together
Not at the concert
不是去演唱會
Okay
Yeah
Thank you
謝了
Thanks
謝謝
Yeah
So, the Ebola virus, that's gotta suck, huh?
那個依波拉病毒… 得到一定很慘
Gee, Monica, what's in the bag?
摩妮卡，袋子裡有什麼？
I don't know, Chandler, let's take a look
不知道，錢德 咱們看一下吧
Oh, it's like a skit
像在演短劇
Why, it's dinner for six, five steaks, and an eggplant for Phoebe
是六個人的晚餐 五塊牛排…
Ooh
Yeah, we switched meat suppliers at work, and the new guys gave me the steaks as sort of a thank you
我們餐廳換了肉食供應商 新供應商送了我這些牛排謝我
But wait, there's more
Hey, Chandler, what is in that envelope?
等等，還有啊… 錢德，那信封裡頭還有什麼？
By the way, this didn't seem so dorky out in the hall
對了，剛才在外面排演 那沒麼驢的
Come on
那走吧
Why, it's six tickets to Hootie and the Blowfish
是六張去看 「混混與自大狂」的票
The Blowfish
是「自大狂」呀
It's on us, all right, so don't worry, this is our treat
是我們付錢的，所以別擔心 我們…
So, thank you
謝謝
Could you be less enthused?
你們能不能更不起勁兒啊
Look, it's a nice gesture
各位，你們一番好意
It is
But it just feels like
可是我們覺得這像…
Like?
像…
Charity
施捨？
Charity?
We're just trying to do a nice thing here
我們只是想讓大家高興
Yeah, but Ross, you have to understand, your nice thing makes us feel about this big
對，羅斯但是你這麼做 讓我們覺得我們很渺小
Actually, it makes us feel that big
事實上，我們是這麼小
I don't understand, I mean, it's like we can't win with you guys
我不懂 我是說，我們怎樣做都不對
Yeah, I mean, if you guys feel this big, maybe that's not our fault, maybe that's just how you feel
若你們覺得那麼渺小的話 那或許不是我們的錯
Oh
Now you're telling us how we feel
你要告訴我們有什麼感受
God, see, okay, we never should have talked about this
你看嘛，我們根本就不該提的
All right, I'm gonna pass on the concert, because I'm just not in a very Hootie place right now
因為我現在 不太有心情去「混」
Me neither
我也是 我也是
Me too
Guys, we bought the tickets
各位，我們票都已經買好了
Oh, well, then you'll have extra seats, you know, for all your tiaras and stuff
那你們就有座位 可以放頭冠啊什麼的
Why did you look at me when you said that?
你說的時候幹嘛瞪著我看？
So, I guess now we can't go
這下子我們都不能去了
What, come on, you do what you want to do, what, we always have to do everything together?
你們去做你們要做的事啊 我們非得集體行動不可嗎？
You know what? You're right
知道嗎？你說得對耶
Fine
很好
All right
好吧
We're gonna go
我們就去
It's not for another six hours?
不過還有六個小時 我們到時候再去
We're gonna go then
我們就去
Chandler
Yeah
Oh, Jesus
Are you ready?
天啊，你準備好了嗎？
Yes, yes, let me grab my jacket and tell you I had sex today
好了，等我先拿個外套 還有我今天上床了
Whoa, whoa, whoa
What, you, you had sex today?
什麼？你今天上床了？
Wow, it sounds even cooler when somebody else says it
從別人嘴裡說出來更酷耶
I was awesome, okay? She was biting her lip to stop from screaming
我棒透了，我害得她必須要 咬住嘴唇忍住尖叫
Wow
Now, I know it's been a while, but I took that as a good sign
我知道我很久沒有這樣了 但我認為那是個好現象
Still doing the screening thing?
你還在過濾電話嗎？
I had sex today
我今天上床了
I never have to answer that phone again
我再也不用去接那個電話
It's up to me, you know what to do
嗶一聲過後，你知道怎麼做
Hey, Bob, it's Jade
小包，我是小潔，聽著
Listen, I just wanted to tell you that I was really hurt when you didn't show up the other day
你那天放我鴿子 我心裡難過極了
And just so you know, I ended up meeting a guy
結果你知道嗎？ 我認識了另一個人
Bob here
我是小包
Oh, hi
So, uh, you met someone, huh?
你認識了別人？
Yes, yes I did
沒錯
In fact, I had sex with him two hours ago
事實上 我兩小時前跟他上床了
So, uh, how was he?
他怎麼樣呢？
Eh
Eh?
Oh, Bob, he was nothing compared to you
小包，跟你比他算什麼
I had to bite my lip to keep from screaming your name
我得咬住嘴唇 才能不叫出你的名字
Well, that makes me feel so good
很高興聽你這麼講
It was just so awkward and bumpy
我是覺得他好沒技巧
Well, maybe he had some kind of, uh, new, uh, cool style that you're not familiar with
或許是因為他採取了一些 你不熟悉的新的酷姿勢
And, uh, maybe you have to get used to it
你應該要習慣他的做法呀
Well, there really wasn't much time to get used to it, if you know what I mean
根本沒多少時間可以讓我習慣…
You know what?
知道嗎？你說得對耶
I'm not going to be able to enjoy this
知道嗎？ 我想我根本沒有心情聽這個
Yeah, I know, it's my birthday, we all should be here
我知道，這是我的生日 我們應該全部在一起的
So let's go
那麼走吧
Well, Nick, you know, maybe we should thank them for one song
或許我們應該聽一首再走
Yeah, I mean, it'd be rude to them for us to leave now
對呀，反正現在離開 對他們有點不敬
You know, the guys are probably having a great time
說不定 他們現在正玩得很開心呢
Come on, you guys, one more time
來吧，再來一次嘛
Okay
One
—
No
不行
That was amazing
Excellent, that was excellent
I can't believe the guys missed us
真不能相信他們錯過這個
What guys? Oh, yeah
你說誰？對了
Excuse me
You're Monica Geller, aren't you?
你會朝我的魚打噴嚏 對不對？
How much?
Do I know you?
You used to be my babysitter
Oh, my God, little Stevie Fisher?
天啊，我的小費史提
How have you been?
近來好不好啊？
Good, good, I'm a lawyer now
很好，我現在是律師了
You can't be a lawyer, you're eight
你不可能是律師，你才八歲
Well, listen, it was nice to see you
I got to run backstage
Wait, backstage?
等等，後台？
Oh, yeah, my firm represents the band
他們是我公司代理的
Ross Chandler
Look, you guys want to meet the group?
你們想認識他們嗎？
Yeah, we do
Come on
那走吧
So, look, are you one of the ones that fooled around with my dad?
對了 你以前也有跟我爸亂搞嗎？
Oh, hey
Hey, you guys
各位
Happy birthday
生日快樂
Oh, thank you, thanks
謝謝
So, uh, how was your night last night?
你們昨天晚上過得怎麼樣？
Oh, well, it pretty much sucked
昨晚真是爛得可以了 你們呢？
How was yours?
你們昨天晚上過得怎麼樣？
Yeah, ours pretty much sucked, too
我們也是爛得可以啊
Oh, but I did run into little Stevie Fisher, do you remember him?
但是我碰到了小費史提 你記得嗎？
Oh, yeah, I used to babysit him
記得，我以前當過他的褓姆
Hey, how's his dad?
他爸好嗎？
Good
很好
Well, aside from that, the whole evening was pretty much a bust
除此之外 我們昨天整個晚上都滿淒慘的
Yeah, we really missed you guys
對，我們很想念你們
Yeah, look, we were just saying, this whole thing is so stupid
對呀，我們剛才還說 這件事太愚蠢了
We just have to really, really, really not let stuff like this about money get, like
我們必須真的真的 不讓錢這種事情介入…
Is that a hickey?
那是個吻痕嗎？
Oh, no, I just, I fell down
On someone's lips?
跌在別人嘴上？
Where'd you get the hickey?
你那吻痕哪兒來的？
You know, a party or
你知道，派對啊…
What party?
什麼派對？
Well, it wasn't a party so much as a, a gathering of people
那不算是派對…
With food and music and, and, and the band
有吃的，有音樂，還有…
Oh
You partied with Hootie and the Blowfish?
你們跟「混混與自大狂」混？
Yes, apparently Stevie and Hootie are like this
對，很顯然史提跟混混是死黨
Who gave you that hickey?
那吻痕是誰給的？
That would be the work of a Blowfish
是其中一個自大狂弄的
Oh
I can't believe it, I can't believe this
我真不敢相信
It's awkward, it's like sitting at home and just trying to guess Joey's fingers and
我們只是坐在家裡頭 猜喬伊的手指頭…
And you guys are out like partying and having fun and, you know, I'll
而你們卻跑出去瘋狂作樂說：
Hey, Blowfish, suck on my neck
「自大狂吸我脖子」
Oh
Hey, look, don't blame us, you guys could have been there, you know
不要怪我們 本來你們也可以去的
Oh, what, as part of your poor friend's outreach program?
什麼？當被你們施捨的 窮朋友，是不是？
But great, it's work
帥，是公司
Look, I don't know what to say, I'm, I'm sorry that we make more money than you
我不曉得該說什麼 很抱歉我們賺的錢比你們多
But we're not gonna feel guilty about it, we work really hard for it
可是我們不想因此有罪惡感 我們很努力的賺錢啊
And we don't work hard?
我們就不努力？
Yeah, hi, it's Monica, I just got a page
我是摩妮卡 剛剛有人CALL我
I'm just saying that we, sometimes we like to do stuff that costs a little more
有時候我們會想做 比較花錢的事情嘛
Oh, and you feel like we hold you back?
是我們拖住你了
Yes
什麼事？
No
不行
Leon, Leon, wait, wait, shh, guys
Wait, I don't understand, those steaks were just a gift from the meat vendor
那些牛排只是肉商送來的禮物
That was not a kickback
可不是回扣啊
All right, I mean, come on, I'll just replace them and we can forget the whole thing
那我買回去還他們 我們把這件事忘掉好了
What corporate policy?
什麼公司政策啊？
No
不行
Yeah
Okay
I just got fired
我被開除了
Oh
Oh, what?
Hi
Here's your check, that'll be $4.12
你們的帳單，一共四塊兩毛
Let me get that
我來付
You got five bucks
你有沒有五塊啊？
Here comes the beep, you know what to do
嗶一聲過後，你知道怎麼做
Hi, it's me
是我
Listen, Bob, I'm probably way out of line here
小包 也許我不該做這樣的要求
I mean, it has been three years
And you're probably seeing someone else now
我是說都過三年了 說不定你另外有女朋友了…
But if we could just have one night together
…我們如果能在一起一個晚上 看在往日的份上…
Just for old times' sake
One hot, steamy, wild night
乾柴烈火的一晚…